Guide to the Student Government Association Records RG 5.15
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series Appendix: Photographs, 40837
  - #49-Hewitt, Carey (?) & Cheryl Lettenberger, 1979; 40938 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #50-Hines, Ted (coach), 1975; 40937 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #51-"In-between classes", 1978; 40936 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #52-Littl Red Riding Hood scene, 1979; 40935 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #53-Loehr, Katherine, 1974; 40934 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #54-Lynch, Mary, 1979; 40933 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #55-Martin, Dennis Patrick, 1974; 40932 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #56-Martin, Dennis Patrick, ca.1977; 40931 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #57-Michell, Joanne (?) & Catherine Orsini, 1974; 40930 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #58-Pagano, Ron, 1975; 40929 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #59-"Painting the window frame", ca.1978; 40928 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #60-Pavis, David, 1974; 40927 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #61-Pavis David, 1978; 40926 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #62-Phillips, John Aristole, 1979; 40925 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #63-"Riding a tractor", ca.1978; 40924 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #64-Sciucco, Diane, 1979; 40923 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #65-Senior Prom (?), ca.1978; 40922 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #66-Shaker, Peter, 1979; 40921 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #67-"Shopping in the college bookstore", 1978; 40920 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #68-Spring Week performance, 1974; 40919 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #69-"Starting WXCI", ca.1974; 40918 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #70-"Student in class", 1978; 40917 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #71-"Student at Info Desk", ca.1978; 40916 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #72-73-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Aborn, Christina & Joan Harrison-Boughton, 2003; 40915 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #74-75-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Aborn, Christina & Guillermo Rivra, 2003; 40914 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #76-77-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Alpha Delta Pi Sorority, 2003; 40913 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #78-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Amatullo, Michelle & Kevin Geoghegan, 2003; 40912 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #79-Aquilla, Ann Marie & another student, 2003; 40911 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #80-81-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Armstrong, Annie & Jamie Gravius, 2003; 40910 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #82-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Band setting up", 2003; 40909 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #83-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Beckett, Elisa, Tim Doran, Jamie Gravius, & Mack Mathieu, 2003; 40908 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #84-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Bernstein, Rob, 2003; 40907 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #85-86-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Bogart, Amy, 2003; 40906 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #87-88-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Bonfietti, Debbie, Erin Palomba, & Amy Thurston, 2003; 40905 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #89-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Collins, Marty, 2003; 40904 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #90-91-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Collins, Marty, Kevin Gianni, & Genette Nowak, 2003; 40903 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #92-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Croswell, Trish & Betty Wolken, 2003; 40902 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #93-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Davis, Jason & Tammy Hammershoy, 2003; 40901 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #94-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Doran, Tim & family, 2003; 40900 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #95-96-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Doran, Tim and Dr. Paul Simon, 2003; 40899 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #97-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Erickson, Mike, 2003; 40898 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #98-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Female attendees pose for camera", 2003; 40897 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #99-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Female student smiles for camera", 2003; 40896 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #100-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Female students enjoying their meal", 2003; 40895 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #101-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Fearra, Lauren, 2003; 40894 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #102-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Flores, Josh, Jamie Gravius, & Kathlen Kelm, 2003; 40893 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #103-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Four female students pose for camera", 2003; 40892 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #104-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Four members of WCSU seated at table", 2003; 40891 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #105-Student Leadership (5/1/03), '"Four students take time from their meal", 2003; 40890 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #106-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Future student leader", 2003; 40889 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #107-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gerber, Richard & Dr. Richard Sullivan, 2003; 40888 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #108-111-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gravius, Jamie (SGA President), 2003; 40887 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #112-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gravius, Jamie & Dr. Frank Herbert, 2003; 40886 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #113-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gravius, Jamie & Cherisse Harris, 2003; 40885 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #114-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gravius, Jamie & Dr. Kevin Issacs, 2003; 40884 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #115-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gravius, Jamie & Gorge Kain, 2003; 40883 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #116-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gravius, Jamie Nancy Sheehen, 2003; 40882 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #117-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Gravius presents award, 2003; 40881 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #118-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Grossman, Melissa & Kathlen Kelm, 2003; 40880 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #119-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Grossman receives award, 2003; 40879 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #120-122-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Group photographs, 2003; 40878 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #123-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Hall, Larry, 2003; 40877 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #124-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Harris, Cherisse & family, 2003; 40876 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #125-126-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Harris, Cherisse & Dr. Paul Simon, 2003; 40875 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #127-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Kappa Chi Alpha Sorority, 2003; 40874 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #128-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Kornlluk, Joan, 2003; 40873 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #129-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Luciano, Steve & other students, 2003; 40872 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #130-Student Leadership (5/1/03), McDonald, Erin & Janet McDonald, 2003; 40871 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #131-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Minigachos, Joe (coach) & Men's Ice Hockey Team members, 2003; 40870 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #132-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Molina, Christina (?), 2003; 40869 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #133-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Nightmare at Newbury," awarded, 2003; 40868 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #134-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Palomba, Erin, 2003; 40867 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #135-139-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Photographs of the room, 2003; 40866 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #140-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Powers, Sharon & Erin Schilling, 2003; 40865 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #141-142-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Members of PAC, 2003; 40864 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #143-146-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Recognized Students, 2003; 40863 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #147-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Rivera, Guillermo, 2003; 40862 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #148-149-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Roach, James (President of WCSU), 2003; 40861 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #150-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Student wiping off her eyeglasses", 2003; 40860 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #151-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Students look at their gifts", 2003; 40859 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #152-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Three male attendees at their table", 2003; 40858 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #153-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Three male students pose for camera", 2003; 40857 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #154-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Three students enjoying their meal", 2003; 40856 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #155-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Three students seated at table", 2003; 40855 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #156-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Two attendees enjoy their salad", 2003; 40854 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #157-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Two female students pose for camera", 2003; 40853 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #158-Student Leadership (5/1/03), WCSU Deans, 2003; 40852 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #159-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Walsh, Tim & another student, 2003; 40851 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #160-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Woman taking photo of group of students", 2003; 40850 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #161-Student Leadership (5/1/03), Yan, Jin (?), 2003; 40849 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #162-Student Leadership (5/1/03), "Young couple at the ceremony", 2003; 40848 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #163-"Students at Semi-Formal", 1979; 40847 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #164-"Taking down the basketball net", 1979; 40846 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #165-Titus, Douglas P., 1979; 40845 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #166-Western faculty members, ca.1982; 40844 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #167-170-Westside groundbreaking, 1978; 40843 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #171-WXCI-Enginering staff, 1974; 40842 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #172-WXCI-Executive & Operations staff, 1974; 40841 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #173-WXCI-News staff, 1974; 40840 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #174-WXCI-Sports staff, ca.1970; 40839 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #175-Yamin, Robert (?), 1979; 40838 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Series Appendix: Club Constitutions, 57861
  2013/2014 Accession
  - ACCESS (Academic, Cultural and Community Enrichment for Student Scholars), 2001; 58027 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Accounting Association, 1981; 58026 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Advocacy for Progressive Thinking, 2008; 58025 (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Airsoft Club, 2008; 58024 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Alpha Delta Pi, undated; 58023 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Alpha Phi Sigma, undated; 58022 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Alternative Break Club, undated; 58021 (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - American Marketing Association, 1985; 58020 (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - American Sign Language, undated; 58019 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Amnesty International, 1989; 58018 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Animal Cruelty Prevention Club, undated; 58017 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Anime Club, 2005; 58016 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Anthropology Club, undated; 58015 (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - Art Magazine, 1984; 58014 (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Asian American Club, undated; 58013 (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Astronomy and Astrophysics Association, 1989; 58012 (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - Backstage, undated; 58011 (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - BASIC, undated; 58010 (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Bauhaus Art Club, 2005; 58009 (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - Belly Dancing Community, 2010; 58008 (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - Best Buddies, 1995; 58007 (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - Billiards, undated; 58006 (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - Biology, undated; 58005 (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - Black Student Alliance, undated; 58004 (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - Boxing, undated; 58003 (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - Breakdance Team, 2001; 58002 (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - Campus Center Board, undated; 58001 (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - Center Stage, undated; 58000 (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - Charismatic Prayer Group, 1989; 57999 (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - Chemistry, undated; 57998 (Box 28, Folder 79)
  - Chess Club, undated; 57997 (Box 28, Folder 80)
  - Chinese Student Scholars Association, 2000; 57996 (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - Christian Ministry, 1979; 57995 (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - Circle K International, undated; 57994 (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - CLIO: History Journal, undated; 57993 (Box 28, Folder 84)
  - Colleges Against Cancer, undated; 57992 (Box 28, Folder 85)
  - College Republican Club, undated; 57991 (Box 28, Folder 86)
  - Communications Club, undated; 57990 (Box 28, Folder 87)
  - Commuter Students Association, undated; 57989 (Box 28, Folder 88)
  - Computer Science, undated; 57988 (Box 28, Folder 89)
  - CT Education Association (CEA) Student Program, undated; 57987 (Box 28, Folder 90)
  - CT Opposes the War Club, undated; 57986 (Box 28, Folder 91)
  - Creative Theater, undated; 57985 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Criminal Justice, 1984; 57984 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Criminology Club, undated; 57983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - CCA, Cross-Cultural Association, undated; 57982 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Dance Team, undated; 57981 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Dance West, 1973; 57980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Def Poetz Society, undated; 57979 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Delta Gamma Phi, undated; 57978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Delta Mu Delta, Beta Delta Chapter, undated; 57977 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Delta Sigma Theta, 1989; 57976 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Discussion Club, 1989; 57975 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Drill Team, undated; 57974 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Echo (The), undated; 57973 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - English Society, undated; 57972 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Environmental Club, undated; 57971 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Epsilon Tau Sigma, undated; 57970 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - FLAGG (Family and Friends of Lesbians & Gays), 1989; 57969 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Feminist Majority Leadership Alliance, 2001; 57968 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Fencing, undated; 57967 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Finance Club, 1984; 57966 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Focus (Photography Club), 2009; 57965 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Foosball Club, 2001; 57964 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Frisbee Club, 2000; 57963 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - GSA (Gay/Straight Alliance), undated; 57962 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Golf Club, 2010; 57961 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Gospel Choir, undated; 57960 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Student Union, 2007; 57959 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Greek Council, 2005; 57958 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Health Science Club, 1997; 57957 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Herpetology Club, 2008; 57956 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - History Society, undated; 57955 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - HSO, Honors Student Organization, undated; 57954 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Hosshin Club, undated; 57953 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - International Cultural Advisory Council, undated; 57952 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - International Student Association, undated; 57951 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Interracial Awareness Society, undated; 57950 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Inter-Residence Hall Association, 1975; 57949 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Inter Varsity Christian Fellowship, 2009; 57948 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Investment Club, undated; 57947 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Irish Human Rights Now, undated; 57946 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Ives Concert Flutists, 2001; 57945 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Jazz Club, undated; 57944 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Jewish Students Association, undated; 57943 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Kappa Chi Alpha, undated; 57942 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Keyboard Club, 2001; 57941 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - LaCrosse Club, 1984; 57940 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Latin American Student Organization (LASO), 1989; 57939 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Lesbian and Gay Alliance, undated; 57938 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Alliance (LGBA), undated; 57937 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - Litchfield Hall, undated; 57936 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - Management Information Systems Club, undated; 57935 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - Marketing Club, undated; 57934 (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Martial Arts Club, undated; 57933 (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Math Society, undated; 57932 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - Media Production Society, 2000; 57931 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Men's Volleyball Club, undated; 57930 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Meteorology Club, 2007; 57929 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Mock Trial Association, 2009; 57928 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Multiple Realities Club, 2010; 57927 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Music Educator's National Conference, undated; 57926 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Muslim Student Organization, undated; 57925 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - National Association of Black Accountants, undated; 57924 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Newbury Hall, 1977; 57923 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Non-Traditional Student Organization, undated; 57922 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Nubian Culture Club, undated; 57921 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Nursing Club, 1991; 57920 (Box 29, Folder 66)
  - Nursing Honor Society, 1985; 57919 (Box 29, Folder 67)
  - Older Wiser Learners (OWL), undated; 57918 (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Opera Club, undated; 57917 (Box 29, Folder 69)
  - Outing Club, undated; 57916 (Box 29, Folder 70)
  - Paranormal Society, 2008; 57915 (Box 29, Folder 71)
  - Peer Educators, undated; 57914 (Box 29, Folder 72)
  - Phi Mu Alpha Sinfonia, undated; 57913 (Box 29, Folder 73)
  - Photography and Fine Arts Club, 2001; 57912 (Box 29, Folder 74)
  - Pistol Club, undated; 57911 (Box 29, Folder 75)
  - Play-it-by-Ear (a capella) club, 2005; 57910 (Box 29, Folder 76)
  - Political Science Club, undated; 57909 (Box 29, Folder 77)
  - Political Science Journal, 2001; 57908 (Box 29, Folder 78)
  - Pre-Health Professions Club, 1997; 57907 (Box 29, Folder 79)
  - Pride Club (People Redefining Independence through Disabilities Education), undated; 57906 (Box 29, Folder 80)
  - Prisma (Student Art Group), undated; 57905 (Box 29, Folder 81)
  - PAC (Program Activities Council), undated; 57904 (Box 29, Folder 82)
  - PSA (Progressive Student Alliance), undated; 57903 (Box 29, Folder 83)
  - Psi Chi (Nat'l Honor Society in Psychology), 1990; 57902 (Box 29, Folder 84)
  - Psychology Club, undated; 57901 (Box 29, Folder 85)
  - Red All Over (Women's literary magazine), 2009; 57900 (Box 29, Folder 86)
  - Republican Youth Movement, 2002; 57899 (Box 29, Folder 87)
  - Rotoract Club, 2010; 57898 (Box 29, Folder 88)
  - Rugby Club, 1990; 57897 (Box 29, Folder 89)
  - Sigma Chi, 1986; 57896 (Box 29, Folder 90)
  - Sigma Delta Tau, 2009; 57895 (Box 29, Folder 91)
  - Ski Club, undated; 57894 (Box 29, Folder 92)
  - Ski Racing Club, 1989; 57893 (Box 29, Folder 93)
  - Ski/Snowboard Club, undated; 57892 (Box 29, Folder 94)
  - Social Sciences Club, undated; 57891 (Box 29, Folder 95)
  - Spartacus/Sappho, 1981; 57890 (Box 29, Folder 96)
  - S.T.O.R.M.S., Students of Organized Research in Meteorological Sciences, undated; 57889 (Box 29, Folder 97)
  - Student Action League for Our Children, undated; 57888 (Box 29, Folder 98)
  - S.A.D.D., Students Against Drunk Driving, 1991; 57887 (Box 29, Folder 99)
  - SCB, Student Center Board, undated; 57886 (Box 29, Folder 100)
  - Student Honors Council, undated; 57885 (Box 29, Folder 101)
  - Students of Human Resources/Management Club, 1983; 57884 (Box 29, Folder 102)
  - Student Management Association, undated; 57883 (Box 29, Folder 103)
  - Student Veterans Organization, undated; 57882 (Box 29, Folder 104)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon, 1991; 57881 (Box 29, Folder 105)
  - Thomas Jefferson Society, 1991; 57880 (Box 29, Folder 106)
  - Up 'til Dawn, undated; 57879 (Box 29, Folder 107)
  - WestConn Cheerleaders, undated; 57878 (Box 29, Folder 108)
  - WestConn Habitat for Humanity, undated; 57877 (Box 29, Folder 109)
  - WestConn Improv Group, undated; 57876 (Box 29, Folder 110)
  - WestConn Writers Club, undated; 57875 (Box 29, Folder 111)
  - WISAO, Western Indian Student Awareness Organization, undated; 57874 (Box 29, Folder 112)
  - Winter Activities Union, 2009; 57873 (Box 29, Folder 113)
  - Womens Soccer Club, 1989; 57872 (Box 29, Folder 114)
  - Wrestling Club, 1989; 57871 (Box 29, Folder 115)
  - WXCI, Western Campus Broadcasting Association, undated; 57870 (Box 29, Folder 116)
  - Yacht Club, 1985; 57869 (Box 29, Folder 117)
  - Yearbook, undated; 57868 (Box 29, Folder 118)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF), 2002; 57867 (Box 29, Folder 119)
  - Youth for Justice, undated; 57866 (Box 29, Folder 120)
  - Zeta Beta Tau, undated; 57865 (Box 29, Folder 121)
    Does not contain a club constitution
  - Zeta Iota Theta, undated; 57864 (Box 29, Folder 122)
  - Running Club, 2008; 57863 (Box 29, Folder 123)
  - Fairfield Hall, 1963; 57862 (Box 29, Folder 124)
    Contains house rules
- Club Updates, 2008-2009
  - Annual Updates, 2008-2009 (Box 29, Folder 25-26)
  - Annual Updates, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Series Appendix: SGA meeting tapes, 58038
  Separated Materials
  Inventory of Damaged Tapes (Inaudible)* 1999: April 26 – one cassette; May 11 – one cassette
  2000: May 8 – cassettes #2 and #3; Oct. 9 – one cassette; Oct 11 – cassettes #2 and #3; Oct. 23 – cassettes #1, #2; and #3; Nov. 6 – cassettes #1 and #2; Nov. 13 – cassettes #1 and #2; Nov. 27 – cassettes #1 and #2; Dec. 13 – cassettes #1 and #2
  2001: April 12 – cassette #2; April 16 – cassettes #1 and #2
  2006: Feb. 13 – one cassette
  2007: Sept. 10 – cassettes #1 and #2; Sept. 24 – cassettes #1 and #2; Oct. 8 – one cassette; Oct. 22 – one cassette; Nov. 19 – cassette #1 and #2; Dec. 3 – one cassette; Unknown Dates/Years; 7 cassettes
  * Note: Only regular cassettes sustained damage; microcassettes remained audible.
  - SGA meeting recordings, 1994; 58047 (Box 30, Item 1)
    Tape set 1: Jan. 30 - three microcassettes | Tape set 2: May 16 - two microcassettes | Tape set 3: Aug. 29 - two microcassettes | Tape set 4: Sept. 12 - three microcassettes | Tape set 5: Sept. 26 - two microcassettes | Tape set 6: Oct. 10 - three microcassettes | Tape set 7: Oct. 24 - three microcassettes | Tape set 8: Nov. 7 - one microcassette | Tape set 9: Nov. 21 - two microcassettes
  - SGA meeting recordings, 1995; 58046 (Box 30, Item 2)
    Tape set 1: June 15 - one microcassette marked "Budget" | Tape set two: Aug. 29 - one microcassette | Tape set 3: Sept. 11 - two microcassettes | Tape set 4: Sept. 25 - two microcassettes | Tape set 5: Oct. 9 - one microcassette | Tape set 6: Nov. 6 - one microcassette | Tape set 7: Dec. 4 - one microcassette
  - SGA meeting recordings, 1996; 58045 (Box 30, Item 3)
    Tape set 1: Jan. 29 - one microcassette | Tape set 2: Feb. 12 - one microcassette | Tape set 3: Feb. 26 - one microcasette | Tape set 4: March 25 - two microcassettes | Tape set 5: April 8 - two microcassettes |Tape set 6: April 22 - one microcassette | Tape set 7: April 29 - one microcassette | Tape set 8: May 6 - one microcassette | Tape set 9: May 13 - one microcassette | Tape set 10: suspected to be Dec. 5 - one microcassette
  - SGA meeting recordings, 1997; 58044 (Box 30, Item 4)
    Tape set 1: Feb. 24 - one cassette | Tape set 2: March 10 - one cassette
  - SGA meeting recordings, 1998; 58043 (Box 30, Item 5)
    Tape set 1: Jan. 19 - one cassette | Tape set 2: Jan. 26 - one cassette | Tape set 3: Sept. 27 - one cassette | Tape set 4: Nov. 23 - two cassettes | Tape set 5: Dec. 7 - one cassette
  - SGA meeting recordings, 1999; 58042 (Box 30, Item 6)
    Tape set 1: Feb. 22 - two cassettes | Tape set 2: March 8 - one cassette | Tape set 3: April 12 - two cassettes | Tape set 4: May 3 - one cassette | Tape set 5: Dec. 6 - one cassette | Tape set 6: date unknown; some noise
  - SGA meeting recordings, 2000; 58041 (Box 30, Item 7)
    Tape set 1: Feb. 7 - one cassette | Tape set 2: Feb. 21 - one cassette (noted "special meeting" | Tape set 3: Feb. 28 - one cassette (two other tapes missing) | Tape set 4: - March 13 - three cassettes | Tape set 5: March 27 - two cassettes | Tape set 6: April 10 one cassette (one missing) | Tape set 7: April 24 - one cassette (one missing) | Tape set 8: May 8 - one cassette | Tape set 9: Aug. 21 - one cassette (two missing) | Tape set 10: Sept. 11 - two cassettes (one missing)
  - SGA meeting recordings, 2004; 58040 (Box 30, Item 8)
    Tape set 1: April 12 - one cassette
  - SGA meeting recordings, undated; 58039 (Box 30, Item 9)
    Tape set 1: Unknown dates - three microcassettes